

CONTACT

Krokuvos Street, 59 - 2 **Vilnius**

agne.siupsinskaite@gmail.com

+370 618 51 542

PROFICIENCES

LITHUANIAN LANGUAGE - C2 ENGLISH LANGUAGE - C1 GERMAN LANGUAGE - B1

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR - HIGH ADOBE PHOTOSHOP - BASIC ADOBE INDESIGN - BASIC

MICROSOFT OFFICE - HIGH MAILCHIMP NEWSLETTER PLATFORM - HIGH CUSTOMER SERVICE - HIGH

AGNĖ ŠIUPŠINSKAITĖ

EDUCATION

2009-2014 VYTAUTAS MAGNUM GYMNASIUM

KLAIPĖDA, LITHUANIA

2014-2018 VILNIUS UNIVERSITY, COMMUNICATION FACULTY

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN PUBLISHING AND MARKETING

VILNIUS, LITHUANIA

ABOUT

I consider myself a flexible individual seeing that I have worked both in teams and individuals with good and consistent results.

I have good time management skills and perform tasks on time in order of priority.

I am a communicative and optimistic person, therefore I get along with people.

I am consistently striving to improve and learn something new.

EXPERIENCE

Publishing house "Vyturys" 2015 - 2015

Marketing trainee;

Data systemization and archiving; data mining; social media management; devising of social media marketing strategies; partial administration of Wordpress.

Perfume boutique "Creme de la Creme" 2016-2017 Seller-consultant;

Customer service; English language improvement; money management; continuous knowledge of perfumery.

3D model marketplace "CGTrader" 2017-2017 Marketing trainee;

Email marketing; social media management; content marketing; blog writing; competitor analysis; data mining; newsletter writing.

Chemical manufacturing company "Calvatis" 2017-2018 Sales director assistant;

Packaging layout; communicating with clients; data mining; product bidding; preparation of orders from Germany.